[{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980266111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":11347,"timeElapsed":61457},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980269604,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3490,"timeElapsed":64950},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980272366,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2759,"timeElapsed":67711},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980280720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":8352,"timeElapsed":76066},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980299934,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":19211,"timeElapsed":95280},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980310686,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":10750,"timeElapsed":106032},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980321540,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":10851,"timeElapsed":116886},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980330324,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8781,"timeElapsed":125670},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980335439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"64","question":"What tradition or custom did your family have that you thought was normal until you realized it was not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5113,"timeElapsed":130785},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980363068,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":8910,"timeElapsed":158414},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980369928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":6858,"timeElapsed":165273},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980372788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":2858,"timeElapsed":168134},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980382347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":9557,"timeElapsed":177693},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980386703,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4354,"timeElapsed":182049},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980396960,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":10255,"timeElapsed":192306},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980401110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4148,"timeElapsed":196456},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980405232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":4121,"timeElapsed":200578},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980409848,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":4614,"timeElapsed":205193},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980428224,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":8659,"timeElapsed":223570},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980431332,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3107,"timeElapsed":226678},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980434990,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3654,"timeElapsed":230336},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980440104,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":5112,"timeElapsed":235450},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980444197,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4091,"timeElapsed":239543},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980448529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":4331,"timeElapsed":243875},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980453798,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":5267,"timeElapsed":249144},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980459938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":6138,"timeElapsed":255284},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980464629,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":4689,"timeElapsed":259975},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980468982,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"222","question":"When was the last time you stopped to appreciate nature? Describe where you were and what you were doing.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":4351,"timeElapsed":264328},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980544211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5964,"timeElapsed":339557},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980546633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2419,"timeElapsed":341978},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980549346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2712,"timeElapsed":344692},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980555708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6360,"timeElapsed":351054},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980559371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":3660,"timeElapsed":354716},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565136,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":5763,"timeElapsed":360482},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980570773,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5635,"timeElapsed":366119},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980575069,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":1,"rt":4294,"timeElapsed":370415},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980579218,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"79","question":"What famous person do you think you would be great friends with if you met?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":4147,"timeElapsed":374564},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631178,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7261,"timeElapsed":426524},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980635088,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3908,"timeElapsed":430434},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980638126,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3035,"timeElapsed":433471},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980643514,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":5387,"timeElapsed":438860},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647121,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":3604,"timeElapsed":442467},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980652904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5781,"timeElapsed":448250},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980655718,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2813,"timeElapsed":451064},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664575,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8854,"timeElapsed":459921},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668335,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"241","question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":463681},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980671355,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Are you a morning person or a night owl? Has this always been the case? If not, when did this change for you?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3018,"timeElapsed":466701},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980690791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":7291,"timeElapsed":486137},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695105,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4312,"timeElapsed":490451},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980697570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2463,"timeElapsed":492916},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980703736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6164,"timeElapsed":499081},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980707197,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":3459,"timeElapsed":502543},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980714006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":6808,"timeElapsed":509352},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980717498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":3490,"timeElapsed":512844},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980723049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":5550,"timeElapsed":518395},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980727046,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":3994,"timeElapsed":522392},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980795503,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":4930,"timeElapsed":590849},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4671,"timeElapsed":595522},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980803636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3458,"timeElapsed":598982},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980807843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4205,"timeElapsed":603189},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980812000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4155,"timeElapsed":607346},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980816202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4201,"timeElapsed":611548},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980819371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3166,"timeElapsed":614717},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980825565,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":6193,"timeElapsed":620911},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980829439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"107","question":"Would you get along with a perfect copy of yourself? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3872,"timeElapsed":624785},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980836050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":5401,"timeElapsed":631396},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980840160,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4109,"timeElapsed":635506},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980843516,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":3354,"timeElapsed":638862},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980849959,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6440,"timeElapsed":645305},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980854287,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":4326,"timeElapsed":649633},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980856937,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2648,"timeElapsed":652283},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980859142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":2203,"timeElapsed":654488},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980863927,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4783,"timeElapsed":659272},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"169","question":"Have you ever had a nickname? How did you get it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":2431,"timeElapsed":661705},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980887805,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6883,"timeElapsed":683151},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980893056,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":5249,"timeElapsed":688402},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980897834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":4776,"timeElapsed":693180},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980903980,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":6144,"timeElapsed":699326},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980908683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4702,"timeElapsed":704029},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980913645,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4960,"timeElapsed":708991},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980916696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3050,"timeElapsed":712042},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980922961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":6263,"timeElapsed":718307},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980927863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"112","question":"What philosophy do you live by? What influences your major decisions in life? Are there people who you think share your philosophy?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4900,"timeElapsed":723209},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980968236,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":97,"rt":8008,"timeElapsed":763582},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980972469,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4231,"timeElapsed":767815},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980975942,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":3471,"timeElapsed":771288},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980985238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":9295,"timeElapsed":780584},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980989450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":4209,"timeElapsed":784796},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980995911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6459,"timeElapsed":791257},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980998632,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":2719,"timeElapsed":793978},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981005935,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":7301,"timeElapsed":801281},{"subjectID":"v7l0bl72pk","prolificID":"6706e4356c23b23ac23420d7","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b25d58f7399c8aa25fc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734981009073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3137,"timeElapsed":804419}]